const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '123 + 148 =', answer: '271', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '214 + 167 =', answer: '381', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '305 + 186 =', answer: '491', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '413 + 128 =', answer: '541', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '572 + 119 =', answer: '691', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '462 + 319 =', answer: '781', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '583 + 218 =', answer: '801', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '345 + 648 =', answer: '993', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '326 + 145 =', answer: '471', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '234 + 159 =', answer: '393', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];